export const graphsData = {
    definition: " A graph is a non-linear data structure that consists of a set of nodes (also called vertices) and a set of edges that connect these nodes. Nodes can represent entities or objects, while edges represent relationships between them. Graphs are versatile data structures that can be used to model a wide variety of real-world problems and situations.",
    explanation: "A graph is an abstract data structure that represents a collection of interconnected objects, called nodes or vertices, and the connections between them, known as edges. These nodes and edges can be interconnected in various ways, forming a complex network of relationships.",
    questions: [
        {
            title: "Island Perimeter",
            id:"463",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/island-perimeter/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0463/?h=463",
        },
        {
            title: "Verifying an Alien Dictionary",
            id:"953",
            difficulty: "Easy",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/verifying-an-alien-dictionary/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0953/?h=953",
        },
        {
            title: "Number of Islands",
            id:"200",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/verifying-an-alien-dictionary/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0200/?h=200",
        },
        {
            title: "Max Area of Island",
            id:"695",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/max-area-of-island/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0695/?h=695",
        },
        {
            title: "Count Sub Islands",
            id:"1095",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/count-sub-islands/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1095/?h=1095",
        },
        {
            title: "Pacific Atlantic Water Flow",
            id:"417",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/pacific-atlantic-water-flow/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0417/?h=417",
        },
        {
            title: "Surrounded Regions",
            id:"130",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/surrounded-regions/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0417/?h=417",
        },
        {
            title: "Reorder Routes to Make All Paths Lead to the City Zero",
            id:"1466",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/reorder-routes-to-make-all-paths-lead-to-the-city-zero/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1466/?h=1466",
        },
        {
            title: "Rotting Oranges",
            id:"994",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/rotting-oranges/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0994/?h=994",
        },
        {
            title: "Snakes and Ladders",
            id:"909",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/snakes-and-ladders/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0909/?h=909",
        },
        {
            title: "Open the Lock",
            id:"752",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/open-the-lock/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0752/?h=752",
        },
        {
            title: "Find Eventual Safe States",
            id:"802",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/find-eventual-safe-states/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0802/?h=802",
        },
        {
            title: "Course Schedule",
            id:"207",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0207/?h=207",
        },
        {
            title: "Course Schedule II",
            id:"210",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule-ii/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0210/?h=210",
        },
        {
            title: "Course Schedule IV",
            id:"1462",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/course-schedule/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1462/?h=1462",
        },
        {
            title: "Check if Move is Legal",
            id:"1958",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/check-if-move-is-legal/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/1958/?h=1958",
        },
        {
            title: "Shortest Bridge",
            id:"934",
            difficulty: "Medium",
            question: "https://leetcode.com/problems/shortest-bridge/",
            answer: "https://walkccc.me/LeetCode/problems/0934/?h=934",
        },
    ]
}